http://www.wwtranslations.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyWorldwide Translations (“WWT,” a brand of Blaha International Group, Inc.) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Our Privacy Policy explains when and why we collect your personal information when visiting our website or directly accessing our services. We review our Policy periodically and update as required. By using our website, you’re agreeing to be bound by this Policy. Any questions regarding this Policy and our privacy practices should be sent by email to: corporate@wwtranslations.com or, in writing to: 2994 Marble Cliff Court, Henderson, NV 89052.Who Is WWT?WWT works as a language translation company, with a registered address at: 2994 Marble Cliff Court, Henderson, Nevada 89052. We offer our services to help businesses and government agencies communicate with their international and internal customers by providing language translations and access to related services including: cultural consulting on marketing campaigns, written translations, spoken and sign language interpreting, audio recording and subtitling, plus localization of websites, eLearning materials and individuals requesting translation of personal documents.How Does WWT Collect Your Information?WWT respects your individual privacy and values the confidences of its clients. We obtain information about you when you use our website, (including our secure customer and vendor portals), when you directly contact us about services, when you submit information requests and supply documents or other attachments and when you pay for services. We only collect your information for legitimate business purposes.What Type of Information Does WWT Collect?Personal information that we may collect for legitimate interests can include your name, company name, title, telephone number, address and email address, or, IP address. You may also directly send us source or reference materials and attachments when you request our language services. Information WWT holds in association with your customer account may include your username, password, payment history, project records, customer support inquiries and other documents or attachments used for processing your language projects.How Does WWT Use Your Information?WWT only keeps limited Personal Data in our systems. The information collected is to aid us in conducting legitimate business operations and completing your projects. WWT treats all material and information sent to us as confidential. We may use your information to:Process orders or requests for projects you have submittedComplete any obligations arising from any contracts enteredProcess paymentsProvide customer support and/or servicesNotify you of changes or additions to servicesProcess contracts or applicationsWe are legally required to hold some types of information to fulfill our statutory obligations. We will only hold your personal information on our systems for as long as required for the relevant activity, or as long as is set out in any relevant contract you hold with us.Marketing PartnersWe will not sell, rent, loan or otherwise make available Personal Data available to any Third Party unless required otherwise by law or, in the scope of a registrar, regulatory or financial audit.Third Party Service ProvidersWe may pass some information to our third-party service providers, agents, subcontractors and other associated organizations for the purposes of completing tasks or projects for you, our client. When we use third party service providers, we disclose only personal information that is necessary to deliver the service or complete the project. We have contracts in place that require them to keep your information confidential and secure. We will not release your information to Third Parties unless you request us to do so or, we are required by law.Your ChoicesWWT is serious about your privacy and will only use your personal information for legitimate interests in ways that are for the purposes for which it was originally collected or authorized by you. This includes administering your account and providing the products and services you have requested.WWT clients always have the opportunity to choose (opt in/out) whether their personal information is: (a) disclosed to a non-agent third party or, (b) used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected and/or authorized by the individual.All EU and Swiss citizens/residents have the right to access, update, correct or take their information down at any time. You can choose to change or update your personal data preferences at any time by contacting us by email at: corporate@wwtranslations.com or, in writing to: 2994 Marble Cliff Court, Henderson, NV 89052.Onward TransfersWWT obtains assurances from its agents that they will actively safeguard all personal information consistent with this Policy. Examples of appropriate assurances include: a contract obligating agents to provide a reasonable level of protection and to delete unnecessary information on a regular basis.Accessing and Updating Your Personal InformationYou have the right to ask for a copy of the personal information we hold about you. The accuracy of your information is important to us. In addition to receiving confirmation of your Personal Data contents, you have the right to correct, amend or delete any information at any time.You may do so by contacting us at: Email: corporate@wwtranslations.com, telephone: 702-897-8841 or, by writing to WWT directly: 2994 Marble Cliff Court, Henderson, NV 89052.CookiesWWT website uses cookies. We may use cookies to store your country or language or service preferences. It is possible to switch off cookies by setting your browser preferences. Turning cookies off may result in a loss of functionality when accessing services through our website.WWT is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the United States Federal Trade Commission (FTC). Please note that WWT may be required to disclose an individual’s personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. EFFECTIVE DATE: 09 May 2018We keep this Policy under regular review.
